XianZhu Li

Senior Full-stack Developer

🛮 am a real full-stack developer with both theoretical knowledge and hands-on experience in web development. It's easy to find people promising everything and delivering almost nothing. My major strengths are in giving realistic promises, being responsive and responsible.



- h.j.dream0428@gmail.com
- Henan, China
- S live:.cid.a0a9d906867e58eb

- +86 18411631215
- in linkedin.com/in/xianzhu-li-610904228
- github.com/websmartdream

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full stack Web developer HCL Technologies

09/2015 - 10/2018

Shanghai, China

HCL Technologies Limited provides cybersecurity, cloud consulting & SI, IT managed services, IT strategy consulting, and more.

joined 4 Websites development

- Responsible for rebuilding the responsive front-end UI using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and React. The new UI greatly improved the user experience.
- Implement testing and debugging logic by writing MySQL Queries and embedded into back-end service.
- Handled async HTTP request/response using JavaScript, Promise, and Ajax.
- Designed and built an accompanying RESTful API in Strapi that unifies data from multiple sources.

Full stack Developer | Front-end team leader

Ann Michaels Ltd

05/2018 - 04/2021

Naperville, United State

Team Leader

- Develop Shopify apps using React.js, GraphQL, Apollo, Nest.js, MongoDB.
- Developed responsive front-end UI using CSS, SASS, MUI (Material UI), and Bootstrap.
- Re-built React Components using React Class Component, Functional Components, State, Props, and React Lifecycle methods.
- Implemented dynamic customer feedback forms using React.js and JavaScript.

EDUCATION

Tsinghua University

Computer Science and Technology

09/2010 - 06/2015

Beijing, China

Courses

- Computer Science
- Operating System
- Database System
- Software engineering
- Algorithm
- artificial Intelligence

SKILLS

React.js/Next.js			•
Vue.js			
Angular			0
Ethereum		0	0
Smart Contract			0
Solidity		0	0
NFT		0	0
MySQL			
PostgreSQL			0
Node.js			
JavaScript			
PHP			
TypeScript			
MongoDB			
Shopify			
CSS/SCSS/LESS			

LANGUAGES

Chinese			
English			0

INTERESTS

Music Skiing Skating Sports